cyware.com 2019-08-06

# Privacy Policy | Cyware

This Privacy Policy shall be read in conjunction and together with the Terms of Use available on [www.cyware.com/tnc](https://cyware.com/tnc) and forms an integral part of the user agreement between You and the Company. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meaning attributed to them under the Terms of Use.

By accessing and/or using the Service, You signify Your agreement to accept this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OR ALL OF THE FOLLOWING TERMS OF THE PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS AND/OR USE THE SERVICE.

Providing information to Us is Your choice. You understand that any data, information, content or information that You post, submit or upload to the Service shall be visible to other Users of the Service and will be stored on Company’s servers for the purposes of making the Service available to You. We advise You to be selective about what information You post. Please do not post, submit or upload to the Service any data, information, content or information which would include any Personal Information and Sensitive Personal Data or Information that You do not wish to be made available to the Company or to the public at the large.

If You do not agree with any or all of the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not provide any information to Us. If at any time You wish to discontinue Your access of the Service, You are free to do so. Further, if You require You can choose to have the Personal Information provided by You deleted by writing to [contact[@]cyware[.]com](mailto:contact@cyware.com). You always have the choice to opt-out of receiving communications from the Service by writing to [contact[@]cyware[.]com](mailto:contact@cyware.com).

We reserve the right, at Our sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Such changes and/or modifications shall become effective immediately upon being posted/published on the Service herein.

Please review the Privacy Policy from time-to-time. Your continued use of the Service following the posting of changes and/or modifications will constitute Your acceptance of any revised Privacy Policy. The Company retains the right at any time to deny or suspend access to all or part of the Service to anyone who the Company believes has violated any condition of this Privacy Policy.

The terms "Personal Information" and "Sensitive Personal Data or Information" shall have the meaning ascribed to it under the Act and/or The Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures And Sensitive Personal Data Or Information) Rules, 2011 and/or any other rules under the Act.

#### 1\. SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OR INFORMATION

THE COMPANY WILL NEVER ASK YOU AND YOU MUST NEVER PROVIDE SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OR INFORMATION TO THE COMPANY OR TO ANY PERSON/ENTITY REPRESENTING THE COMPANY. ANY DISCLOSURE OF SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OR INFORMATION SHALL BE AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND WITHOUT ANY LIABILITY TO THE COMPANY (INCLUDING ITS DIRECTORS, KEY MANAGERIAL PERSONNEL, OFFICERS AND EMPLOYEES).

YOU MUST NOT DISCLOSE YOUR:

(i) passwords

(ii) financial information such as bank account details, credit card details, debit card details, secure pin number, passwords, etc.

(iii) physical, physiological and mental health condition

(iv) sexual orientation

(v) medical records and history

(vi) biometric information

(vii) national identification numbers

(viii) and such other sensitive personal data or information.

1.1 Users must note that any information that is freely available or accessible in public domain or furnished under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force shall not be regarded as personal information or sensitive personal data or information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy and the Company shall not be obliged to take any measures to protect the same since the same is freely available in the public domain.

1.2 Please note that identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to the Company. We do not and will not, at any time, request Your credit card information/debit card information/financial pin numbers and passwords.

#### 2.PERSONAL INFORMATION

2.1 The primary purpose of collection of personal information set out in Clause 2 (i) hereinbelow and other information set out in Clause 2.1 (ii) to (viii) hereinbelow, is to allow You to access and use the Service and various features on or in relation to the Service provided by the Company.

(i) We may obtain information about Your name, email address, date of birth, age, device, device id, contact details, gender, location, pin code, area code, occupation, provided by You either on the Service and/or which may be available to the Company or other Users as a result of You publishing User Material on the Service and/or which may be available to the Company if You access the Service through any linked social media platforms;

(ii) We may also obtain information about You, from any e-mails, letters, communication, etc. that You send to Us.

(iii) We may receive information that You submit to any Third-Party Service You access from links contained within the Service. You should check the privacy policy of such Third-Party Websites to find out how they will use Your personal information and sensitive personal data or information. The Company shall not be responsible or liable for use or misuse of the same by Third-PartyWebsites.

(iv) We may obtain information about Your IP address, operating system, browser type, browser version, browser configuration, name of internet service provider, and other types of computer and connection related information relevant to identifying Your type of device, geographic location, usage history, etc.

(v) We may also obtain information about how the Service is used by You. Such information may include but shall not be limited to:

(a) User Material that You publicly post or share on the Service;

(b) login information (date and time of login, number of logins, etc.);

(c) destinations/ pages visited within the Service;

(d) advertisements viewed and measurement of advertisement effectiveness;

(e) content viewed;

(f) content shared;

(g) User preferences (eg. program preferences, language, preferred social media, searched items, etc.);

(h) Third-Party Websites visited while on the Service;

(i) service requests; etc.

(vi) We may also obtain information collected by cookies or similar technologies (as described below), through contest and promotions held by the Company, newsletter subscriptions, enrollment for promotions, campaigns, special offers, surveys, feedback, analytics, research, information posted in social communities on the Service, etc. or otherwise shared on the Service.

(vii) We may also obtain information collected as a result of You hosting, displaying, uploading, modifying, publishing, transmitting, updating and sharing User Materials on the Service.

(viii) If You access the Service through a social media platform, We may collect Your user ID or user name, any information You have permitted the social media service to share with Us, and any information You have made public with the social media service. In such a case, You undertake to comply to the Terms of Use including the Privacy Policy of the Service and any additional terms and conditions stipulated by such social media platforms. In the event of any inconsistency, the Terms of Use including the Privacy Policy of the Service shall prevail to the extent of conflict.

2.2 We may combine Your personal information with information collected from Tracking Technologies and aggregate it with information collected from other Users using the Service to attempt to provide You with the services and a better experience on the Service. You understand, agree and acknowledge that Our collection, storage and processing of Your personal information is for a lawful purpose connected with the functioning of the Service. You hereby consent to the collection, storage, use, disclosure, transfer, processing of the personal information for the purposes set out herein.

2.3 WE MAY DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN THE CIRCUMSTANCES SET OUT BELOW AND YOU HEREBY CONSENT TO THE SAME TO BE SHARED WITH:

(a) any third-party service provider to whom disclosure is necessary to enable Us to provide You with the services which You wish to access on or through the Service;

(b) any third-party service provider to whom disclosure is necessary to enable Us to provide You with the gratification as a result of You participating in any contest, promotional or marketing activity organized by the Company;

(c) any person/entity to whom disclosure is necessary in accordance with applicable law;

(d) any government or statutory authority or court of law or judicial forum to whom disclosure is necessary in accordance with applicable law;

(e) in circumstances We believe necessary or appropriate to respond to valid claims and legal process, to protect the property and rights of the Company, to protect the safety of the public or any person or User, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity;

(f) any person/entity to whom disclosure is necessary to enable Us to enforce Our rights;

(g) to Our joint ventures, business partners, agents or third parties for the purposes of the services or for any other marketing and promotional activity undertaken by or on behalf of the Company;

(h) any entity that legally acquires the Company or its Service.

We will use reasonable efforts to ensure that third parties who provide services in terms of this Clause 2.3, are under an obligation to maintain confidentiality with respect to the personal information and to use it for the purposes of the services only.

We understand the importance of data security and We want Your browsing experience with Us to be as safe as possible. We have implemented reasonable safeguards and precautions to protect Your personal information.

PLEASE UNDERSTAND THAT, WHILE WE STRIVE TO PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA AGAINST POTENTIAL RISKS AND EXPOSURES, THERE IS NO ABSOLUTE SECURITY IN THE ONLINE/ INTERNET SPHERE. THEREFORE, YOU MUST NOT DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION ON THE SERVICE THAT IS SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OR INFORMATION. YOU UNDERSTAND THAT THE TRANSMISSION OF INFORMATION OVER THE INTERNET IS NOT COMPLETELY SECURE AND THERE ARE RISKS ASSOCIATED WITH IT. ALTHOUGH WE STRIVE TO PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, WE CANNOT GUARANTEE THE SECURITY OF THE SAME WHILE IT IS BEING TRANSMITTED TO OUR SERVICE AND ANY TRANSMISSION IS AT YOUR OWN RISK.

#### 3\. COOKIES & WEB BEACONS

3.1 BY DEFAULT, YOUR WEB BROWSER WILL ACCEPT COOKIES, HOWEVER THIS CAN BE ALTERED BY YOU. YOU HAVE THE OPTION OF ENABLING OR DISABLING COOKIES IN YOUR WEB BROWSER. IF YOU DO NOT WANT US TO INSTALL COOKIES, YOU MAY CHANGE THE SETTINGS ON YOUR WEB BROWSER TO DISABLE COOKIES. HOWEVER PLEASE NOTE THAT IF YOU DISABLE COOKIES, YOU MAY NOT BE ABLE TO USE ALL OF THE FEATURES OF THE SERVICE.

3.2 The Service and/or third parties may use "Cookies", "Web Beacons", and other similar tracking technologies (collectively, "Tracking Technologies") to collect information automatically as You browse the Service and the internet. For the purposes of this clause below terms have the meanings as set out below:

"Cookies" (which may be html files, flash files or other technology) are text files that help store user preferences and activity.

Web beacons" (also known as image tags, gif or web bugs) are small codes used to collect advertising data, such as counting page views, promotion views or advertising responses.

3.3 We use Tracking Technologies to help tailor Our content, understand Service and internet usage, improve or customize the content, offerings or advertisements on this Service, personalize Your experience on this Service (for example, to recognize You by name when You return to the Service), save Your password in password-protected areas, save Your online game or video player settings, allow Users to move between associated Services without logging into each Service, help us offer You programs or services that may be of interest to You, deliver relevant advertising, maintain and administer the Service, etc. These Tracking Technologies collect "click stream" data and other additional information regarding Your visits to the Service, such as Your visits to the Service's webpages, use of Our features, or preferences and may also collect Your IP address or some other identifier unique to the device You use to access the Service ("Identifier"). Your Identifier is automatically assigned to the device You use to access the Service. By visiting the Service, whether as a registered user or otherwise, You acknowledge, understand and hereby agree that You are giving us Your consent to track Your activities and Your use of the Service through these Tracking Technologies.

3.4 The Service may additionally use a variety of third party advertising networks, data exchanges, traffic measurement service providers, marketing analytics service providers and other third parties including Adtech, Google and others (collectively, "Third Party Advertising Service Providers") to, for example, serve advertisements on the Service, facilitate targeting of advertisements and/or measure and analyze advertising effectiveness and/or traffic on the Service ("Targeting Services"). These Third Party Advertising Service Providers may enable Us to display advertisements based on Your visits to the Service and other Services You have visited. Targeting Services enable Us to, among other things, help deliver advertisements or other content to You for services that You might be interested in, to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to You, etc.

3.5 The Third Party Advertising Service Providers, as well as advertisers, may themselves set and access their own Tracking Technologies on Your device if You choose to have Tracking Technologies enabled

in Your browser (or, for flash cookies, if You have not removed them) and/or they may otherwise have access to information about You.

3.6 Cookie and IP address information of a request to any Third Party Advertising Service Provider may be transferred to the responding data centers outside the territory of India as well and these may include countries where applicable data protection laws provide a lesser degree of protection than India. By using this Service You consent to the processing of data about You by such Third Party Advertising Service Providers. In the event of any inconsistency, the Terms of Use including the Privacy Policy of the Service shall prevail to the extent of conflict only.

#### 4\. GDPR COMPLIANCE

To support the changes in Europe’s new privacy law, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) that went into effect on May 25, 2018, we have updated our Privacy Policy to make it easier for customers and clients to understand what data we collect, how it is kept secure and what it is used for. Cyware Labs has undertaken a review of its data collection, storage and security arrangements have have taken measures to ensure the core principles of data security and privacy ensconced in GDPR are reflected, including every individual’s right to access their data and right to be forgotten.

Although these changes have been sparked by new EU legislation, we believe privacy and transparency are an important right for all citizens and applies to everyone, regardless of where you’re located.

Your privacy and trust is important to us, and at Cyware, we strive to make our policies, products and services as clear and easy to use as possible. We want to assure all of our customers that are have worked hard to ensure compliance in all areas of our business and have taken measures to meet all legal and compliance specifications with regards to customer data. 

(i) We are not asking to collect more data or plan to use your data any differently. However, we are providing full transparency and specific details on how we use the information we collect and how long we store that data for improved clarity and full transparency.

(ii) We have included explanations for why Cyware processes customer data, the types of data we process and details about your data protection rights.

(iii) We also added more information on who customer data is shared with in order to provide our services to you. 

(iv) You can also review how to update your marketing and newsletter communication preferences and learn how to opt out of them, should you wish to do so. 

4.1 Personal data provided directly to us

Cyware Labs collects personal data from you if and when you request a product or service directly from us. This may be collected when you:

Register on our website

(i) Subscribe to our newsletter(s) or marketing email(s)

(ii) Apply for a job

(iii) Request a demo to learn more about Cyware products

(iv) Sign up for one of Cyware’s security solutions including web apps, iOS and Android mobile apps

(v) Sign up for a content or promotion held by Cyware

(vi) Enroll for promotions, campaigns, special offers, surveys or feedback by Cyware

The information we routinely collect when you register on our website or subscribe to our newsletters include basic information such as full name, company designation and email address. In some cases, specific information relevant for a particular service are collected such as phone number, profile picture and city/country may be required. Alternatively, you may sign in using your Gmail account and authorize Google to fetch your information. 

4.2 When you visit our websites

When you visit our website for the first time, you will receive a pop-up notice informing you that we use Cookies. Some personal data such as a unique identifier, your IP and address and geographical data will be collected through our or other technologies’ use of cookies to help us understand how you interact with our websites. 

You can also choose to disable your web browser’s ability to accept cookies and how they are set.

4.3 When you visit our service via social media

If you happen to access our service through a social media platform, like Facebook or Twitter, we may collect some information such as user ID or user name and any information you have permitted the social media service to share with us or information you have made public with the social media service. In this case, you have agreed to comply with the Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and any additional terms or conditions of the social media platform. We recommend you check what permissions are enabled in your social media profiles for more information.

4.4 Marketing communications

We will only send you direct marketing communications when you have provided your consent by submitting a form or ticking a box and where we believe we can demonstrate a legitimate business interest in balance with your own interests and privacy.

However, you are always free to stop receiving direct marketing communications from us at any time. You can stop receiving these messages from us at anytime by emailing us directly.

4.5 Newsletter communications

We will only send you Cyware newsletters when you have provided your consent by submitting a form or ticking a box, thereby expressing your interest in receiving the latest news about the field of cybersecurity, new threats and fresh editorial content as they roll in. 

However, you are always free to stop receiving these newsletters from us at any time by emailing us. There is always an unsubscribe link at the bottom of any newsletter you receive from us as well, should you wish to do so.

4.6 Where we store your personal data

We are committed to protecting the security of the personal data we hold. Access to data stored by Cyware is restricted and we have deployed appropriate organizational and technical measures to ensure your data is secure to prevent any unauthorized access.

We have ensured that your personal data is encrypted and stored on our secure systems. The length of time for which we keep your information varies and depends on the products or services we provide to you. We also have an internal schedule to ensure backups are created and we do not hold your personal data for longer than we justifiably require it. Personal data is only kept for a reasonable period of time and can be readily requested to be amended or deleted by you at any time.

4.7 Access your personal data

You always have a choice to request a copy of the personal data we may hold related to you and the purpose for which we are using it. To ensure you are who you say you are, we may require proof of identity to make sure we do not inadvertently send your personal information to the wrong person. Please use our contact details [insert link] to get in touch with us.

4.8 Amend or delete your personal data.

If you believe your personal data held by us is incorrect or out of date, please let us know via email and we will rectify the issue as soon as personal.

If you wish to have your personal data deleted by us, please let us know via email and we will respond to the request, on a case-by-basis, as soon as possible. By using Cyware and its products on or after May 25th, 2018, you are agreeing to the changes. If you have any questions about these changes, feel free to reach out to us at [contact[@]cyware[.]com](mailto:contact@cyware.com).

#### 5\. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES 

5.1 This Service may contain links to other Services owned and operated by third parties which are not under the control of the Company ("THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES").

5.2 THE SERVICE MAY CONTAIN LINKS TO OTHER THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES WHICH ARE NOT UNDER THE CONTROL OF THE COMPANY. ANY SERVICE YOU VISIT BY A LINK FROM THE SERVICE IS SOLELY THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE THIRD PARTY PROVIDING THE SERVICE. THE CONTENT OF, INCLUDING MATERIALS AND INFORMATION CONTAINED ON, ANY THIRD PARTY SERVICE TO WHICH YOU LINK FROM THE SERVICE IS SOLELY THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE PROVIDER OF THAT THIRD PARTY SERVICE. ANY TRANSACTIONS THAT YOU ENTER INTO WITH A THIRD PARTY LISTED IN THIS SERVICE OR LINKED FROM THIS SERVICE ARE SOLELY BETWEEN YOU AND THAT THIRD PARTY. THE COMPANY IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY SUCH THIRD-PARTY SERVICE, ANY PRODUCTS OR SERVICES SOLD OR PROVIDED BY SUCH THIRD PARTY SERVICES, NOR THE ORGANIZATIONS PUBLISHING THOSE THIRD PARTY SERVICES, AND HEREBY DISCLAIM ANY RESPONSIBILITY AND LIABILITY FOR THE SAME. THE INCLUSION OF ANY LINKS DOES NOT CONSTITUTE OR IMPLY AN ENDORSEMENT OR RECOMMENDATION BY US OF THE THIRD-PARTY, OF THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE, ADVICE, INFORMATION OR OTHER MATERIALS DISPLAYED, PURCHASED, OR OBTAINED BY YOU AS A RESULT OF AN ADVERTISEMENT OR ANY OTHER INFORMATION OR OFFER IN OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE THIRD PARTY SERVICE. THE COMPANY AND SERVICE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE, ACCOUNTABLE OR RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND/OR SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OR INFORMATION BEING USED OR MISUSED BY SUCH THIRD-PARTY SERVICE.

5.3 YOUR ACCESS AND USAGE OF ANY THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES IS ENTIRELY AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE COMPANY SHALL NOT BE A PARTY TO ANY TRANSACTION BETWEEN YOU AND A THIRD-PARTYSERVICE.

5.4 Your use of a Third-Party Service is subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policy of that site in addition to these Terms of Use. In the event of any inconsistency between the governing terms and conditions, the Terms of Use including the Privacy Policy of the Service shall prevail to the extent of conflict.

#### 6.SUPPORT

6.1 If You do not consent to any part of the privacy terms herein or wish to withdraw consent to process Your information then You may stop using the Service and ask Us to remove Your information from Our records by writing to [contact[@]cyware[.]com](mailto:contact@cyware.com). However if You so withdraw, We might be unable to provide certain services.

6.2 You may also request to know or edit information about yourself stored with Us by writing to Us at [contact[@]cyware[.]com](mailto:contact@cyware.com).

6.3 You have full control regarding which emails You want to receive. If You decide at any time that You no longer wish to receive such emails from Us, please write to Us instructing an Opt-Out. Please note that

once We receive Your request, it may take an additional period of time for Your opt-out to become effective.

6.4 If You have any further questions, queries, complaints or claims with respect to the Service, then such correspondence should be directed to the grievance officer at [contact[@]cyware[.]com](mailto:contact@cyware.com).
